const STORE = {
  quizItems:[
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is not an ingredient of an Old Fashioned?',
      answers: ['bourbon', 'sweet vermouth', 'sugar', 'bitters'],
      correctAnswer: 'sweet vermouth'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the base spirit in an Aviation?',
      answers: ['vodka', 'gin', 'rum', 'tequila'],
      correctAnswer: 'gin',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which ingredient is not in a Last Word?',
      answers: ['maraschino liqueur', 'green chartreuse', 'absinthe', 'lime juice'],
      correctAnswer: 'absinthe',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the base spirit in a Paloma?',
      answers: ['tequila', 'rum', 'mezcal', 'vodka'],
      correctAnswer: 'tequila',
    },
    {
      question: 'The Sazerac was created in which city?',
      answers: ['Paris, France', 'New York, New York', 'Cleremont, Kentucky', 'New Orleans, Louisiana'],
      correctAnswer: 'New Orleans, Louisiana',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is not an ingredient in a Sidecar?',
      answers: ['simple syrup', 'lemon juice', 'Cointreau', 'cognac'],
      correctAnswer: 'simple syrup',
    },
    {
      question: 'The Rob Roy was introduced in what year?',
      answers: ['1695', '1795', '1895', '1995'],
      correctAnswer: '1895',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is not a type of Collins?',
      answers: ['Tom Collins', 'John Collins', 'Vodka Collins', 'Jim Collins'],
      correctAnswer: 'Jim Collins',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which spirit is an ingredient in a Blood and Sand?',
      answers: ['Irish whiskey', 'aged rum', 'scotch', 'bourbon'],
      correctAnswer: 'scotch',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which came first?',
      answers: ['Cosmopolitan', 'Collins', 'Manhattan', 'Hot Toddy'],
      correctAnswer: 'Hot Toddy'
    }]
};